聚過來，給個看
Gather round, take a look
說說你看到什麼
tell me what you see
寶貝你竟然跑來這樣對我
Baby now you've gone and done it to me
你看穿我眼睛沒？
Can you read my eyes?
有個什麼叫著你
There's something calling you
我有些魔法你非常的感興趣
I've got some magic that you'll be really into
噢...就是這樣
Ohh, just like that
我把你鉤住的眼神
The way I got you watching
你有否被催眠過？
Have you ever been hypnotized?
有否過如此著迷？
Have you ever been so enticed?
你不懂這種的魔法
You don't know this kind of magic
就退下讓我發功
so sit back and let me work
來，歡迎來到魔術秀
So welcome to the magic show
你會一見鍾情
It's love at first sight
所以你就給我跪下
So get right down on you knees
你想求饒也是可以
and you can beg if you please
喔...噢，沒關係
Ohhh, oh, it's okay
好好活滿你的性命
And live your life to the full
別把自己變成蠢蛋
Just don't make yourself a fool
噢，歡迎來到魔術秀
Oh, welcome to the magic show
我看來怎樣？看著還好嗎？
How do I look? Do I look alright?
跟我說我漂亮，很迷人
Tell me I'm pretty, a lovely sight
我這一生都是照他們想要的那樣
All my life I've been told the way they want
心中有一股火焰
Feel a burning in my heart
已不想期盼
Waiting eyes are out
你真的跑來速戰速決
Now you've really gone and done it in bout
不能給大家看恐懼，因為他們不想看恐懼
Can't let them see my fear 'cuz fear isn't what they want
他們想怎樣？
What do they want?
他們到底想怎樣？
What is it that they want?
歡迎來到魔術秀
Welcome to the magic show
不管許什麼願，我都會讓它們成真
Whatever your dreams are, I'll make them come true
所以你就給我跪下
So get right down on you knees
你想求饒也是可以
and you can beg if you please
喔...噢，沒關係
Ohhh, oh, it's okay
好好活滿你的性命
And live your life to the full
別把自己變成蠢蛋
Just don't make yourself a fool
噢，歡迎來到魔術秀
Oh, welcome to the magic show
好好大飽眼福
Feast your eyes on a show
我的巨作
on my creation
看穿你的靈魂，世界遠離你身
Look into your soul, the world is far from here
看著我，我在燈光底下
Look at me I'm in the spotlight
我最棒
I'm the best
我要求你的注意，剩下的就交給我
I demand your attention now and I'll handle the rest
交給我
The rest
因為我就是你夢想的那個人
'Cuz I am the one you wanted all along
不斷為了繼續待在你心上奮戰
I've been fighting for another day inside your mind
因為我就是那個承諾一切的人
'Cuz I am the one who promises everything
這就是我這一生不斷期待的時刻
'Cuz this is the moment I've been waiting for my whole life
大家的臉都盯著我，得趕快想出下一步
The faces all stare at me I've got to do something quick
我可以把他們送進暈眩
I can dazzle them out of their minds
我知道我啥都攔不住
I know nothing can stop me now
但恐懼一刻降到身前
But a moment of dread falls before me
我的人生閃過眼前
My life passes before my eyes
這懼怕吞噬我魂，我一無所有
This terror engulfs my soul and nothing's left at all
所有
At all
因為我就是你夢想的那個人
'Cuz I am the one you wanted all along
不斷為了繼續待在你心上奮戰
I've been fighting for another day inside your mind
因為我就是那個承諾一切的人
'Cuz I am the one who promises everything
這就是我這一生不斷期待的時刻
'Cuz this is the moment I've been waiting for my whole life
噢—戰場高潮，我感覺到
Ooh the thrill of the fight, I feel it now
管啥規矩，我該走了
Fuck the rules it's time to go
我還有什麼準備給你
Got another thing coming to you
等一下你就知道
Just wait a minute and see
你贏不了，你是不是瘋了
You can't win, you'd be out of your mind
但來吧，你大可試試
But step right in, you can try
因為我最愛你們眼神的感覺
'Cuz I'm in love with the feeling of your eyes
盯著我
Staring at me
所以你就給我跪下
So get right down on you knees
你想求饒也是可以
and you can beg if you please
喔...噢，沒關係
Ohhh, oh, it's okay
好好活滿你的性命
And live your life to the full
別把自己變成蠢蛋
Just don't make yourself a fool
噢，歡迎來到魔術秀
Oh, welcome to the magic show